ROBIN TEN BERGE

RTB Projects Leusdenhof 348 1108DT Amsterdam

+31 6 43 90 68 38 robin@rtbprojects.com

http://www.rtbprojects.com http://www.linkedin.com/in/ robintenberge

Technical Skills

NodeJS

Angular 7

Bootstrap 4

Amazon Web Services

CI/CD

Soft Skills

Communicative

Proactive

Problem solving

Team player

Structured

Certificates

Mobile Web Specialist 2019

AWS Developer 2018

Java SE8 2017

Scrum Developer 2016

Profile

Robin is a senior full stack web developer with 10 years experience developing cloud-, frontend- and backend solutions. He is focussed on being productive to deliver high quality products while using best practices. He enjoys helping team members and has a desire to share his gained insights.

Robin has excellent communication skills and knows how to find his way within an organisation. He is a pioneer and takes initiatives to help move an organisation forward with innovation. He embraces new technology, puts them into practice and keeps educating himself.

Scrum Master - "You know how to challenge the team. You have a clear opinion on quality and productivity. And in this way you help bring the team to a higher level."

Product Owner - "Robin is able to take responsibility for a solution. He likes to take the lead in creating a collaborative solution and then also delivers it."

Experience

Senior Consultant, Capgemini, Amsterdam — 2014 - Present Worked as web developer and IT consultant at ABN AMRO in Amsterdam. All assignments were in a complex Agile/Scrum environment with Offshore.

For the Commercial Banking department:

- Created new mobile friendly webpages and integrated multiple platforms into the abnamro.nl/zakelijk website. Managed with SDL Tridion.
- Lead in setting up the frontend architecture utilising the NodeJS ecosystem. Used Bootstrap 4 with custom CSS/Sass for styling. Built functionality with Web Components, Angular 7 and vanilla ES6/ Typescript. Collaborated with other teams to share the architecture.
- Setup a CI/CD pipeline in Jenkins which runs Webpack builds, Jasmine unit tests, Protractor e2e tests and integrates with SonarQube and Nexus.
- Initiated an organisational change to upgrade the Java web application by pitching a Proof of Concept to management. This upgrade is needed to be able to work with DevOps teams.
- Had a business trip to Hyderabad in India to provide knowledge transfer to the Offshore team.

For the Retail department:

- Delivered the first mobile friendly widget for Retail Internet Banking. Managed with Backbase Portal.
- Collaborated with architects on setting up the frontend for the widgets. Used AngularJS 1.6 and Bootstrap 3 as a foundation.

- Followed release processes to deliver widgets and pages to the production environment.
- Setup the framework for unit testing with Jasmine, e2e testing with Protractor and a RESTful stub-server with ExpressJs. Shared it with other teams so they can perform better testing and comply with quality guidelines.
- Setup the foundation of a technical style guide with reusable UI components. Supported other teams in using the frontend architecture and reusable components so they can build and deliver faster.

Senior Consultant, RTB Projects; Amsterdam — 2009 - Present
Self employed with the goal to deliver web development and IT consultancy to small and large companies.

- Created own website rtbprojects.com using VueJs server side rendering on Google Firebase.
- Created a Proof of Concept for growing indoor plants. Built a mobile app with React Native
 which makes a bluetooth connection to a Raspberry Pi. The device then uses custom NodeJs
 scripts to connect to the AWS Internet of Things service.
- Created a bot running on AWS for trading cryptocurrency using a blockchain platform API. To keep the architecture serverless, it uses a CI/CD pipeline and then stores its trade history in DynamoDB.
- Created a full e-commerce solution with PHP to sell products via internet. This includes frontend and a backend for inventory, order and payment processing (woocommerce did not exist yet).
- Provided IT consultancy to other self employed companies. This includes support with webhosting and delivery of new Wordpress websites, SEO and analytics implementation.

Project Leader, Wageningen University & Research; Wageningen — 2012 - 2013

Responsible for two IT projects. One Prince2 project to deliver an IT Selfservice Portal. And a
Scrum project to deliver a workflow application for an internal customer. The activities included
making project plans, supporting the teams and communicating with stakeholders.

Education

Windesheim University of Applied Sciences, Zwolle – Business Information Technology, Bachelor degree - 2005 - 2008

- Graduated with honour and one year shortened.
- Had two internships. One in New Zealand at Jack & Di's Lakeview Accommodation to optimise
 the reservation process and systems (grade: A+). And a final internship at Ernst & Young to
 develop a method to conduct strategic business information planning (grade: A+).

Additional Activities

Interested in other cultures and meeting new people by doing volunteering projects or adventurous travel. For example backpacking in New Zealand (2007) and a hitchhike trip to Asia (2008). Also did a youth leader training in Russia (2012) and performed as group leader for an international volunteering project in The Netherlands (2012).

Trained with a professional youth team at Landstede Basketbal Zwolle (2001 - 2003) and afterwards kept playing basketbal. Since 2014 started training for yearly triathlon races: swim, bike and run.

Skill Matrix	Knowledge (level)		dge	Experience (years)
Frontend				
HTML, CSS and Javascript			Х	10+
Bootstrap 3 and 4 (incl. Sass)			Х	5
NodeJs ecosystem			Х	5
AngularJs and Angular 7 (incl. Ngrx)			Х	4
Jasmine and Protractor		Х		4
ECMAScript 6 and Typescript		Х		2
VueJs/Vuex/Nuxt and React/Redux		Х		1
Web Components and Progressive Web Apps		Х		1
Backend				
ExpressJs			Х	5
RESTful API integrations (JSON or XML)			Х	5
MySQL and MongoDB		Х		5
PHP and Java		Х		5
Linux		Х		4
Platforms				
Wordpress			Х	6
SDL Tridion and Backbase			Х	3
Amazon Web Services		Х		3
Google Cloud Platform (incl. Firebase)		Х		2
Google Digital Marketing (incl. Tag Manager, SEO and Analytics)		Х		6
Practices				
Agile/Scrum			Х	6
CI/CD (Git, Jenkins, Webpack, SonarQube, Nexus and Docker)			Х	4
DevOps		Χ		2